EDINA-CATHERINE SHELDS

Nordic/International Business Developer/Account Executive/GTM Strategist +31681902723 • eshelds89@gmail.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/catherineedina/ • Stockholm/Amsterdam

Summary

I'm from Stockholm, where I studied Statistics and Economics, followed by a semester at NOVA School of Business in Lisbon. After an internship in Munich, I gained international experience in Amsterdam. I specialize in helping innovative high growth businesses expand globally, with 4 years at Oracle as an Account Executive driving business development across diverse industries.

Experience

Shoparize - Google Premium Partner

Remote

Business Development Manager (Promotion after 4 months)

02/2024 - Present

- Shoparize is a leading SAAS CSS in Europe, Google Premium Partner,
- · Full Go-To-Market Strategy in the Nordics and the US, Partner relationship building and growth.
- Individual contributor role and sales manager for partner team.
- Closed record of 40 deals first month average around \$30000 ARR
- Closed record new brand logos in Nordics such as Gina Tricot, Flying Tiger, Desigual, Nokia, Hugo Boss, Kitchenaid and many more.

Fusion worldwide Inc

Account Executive

On-site

11/2022 - 12/2023

- · Fusion is a leading electronic component distributor with over \$3.5 Billion in Revenue (2022) and one of US largest private companies
- Individual contributor role with only new business.
- Strong Sales performance: Exceeded target of \$50KARR/Month with 25% with only own logos.

ORACLE Inc Netherlands, Amsterdam, Hybrid

BDM to Senior Account Executive (Promotion after 2 years)

06/2016 - 06/2020

- · Leading worldwide enterprise software, SAAS, Database technology, and cloud solutions company.
- Promoted from BDM to Senior Account Executive 2018-2020
- Acting as a trusted advisor for Oracle CX Suite and supporting customers in the Nordics and Benelux with their digital transformation for Oracle EMEA, Solutions sales, Consultancy for highly innovative customer experience cloud solutions.
- · Exceeded target of \$840,000 in ARR, with 40% of revenue generated from new business and 60% from account management.

Discovery Networks Sweden

Sweden, Stockholm, on-site

Executive Assistant to the CEO

01/2014 - 01/2015

- The Largest Media house in Sweden and part of Discovery Networks
- · Helped CFO deliver all numbers to their sale to Bauer Media Group during this time period.
- Trainee in Management team for a year

Education

Stockholms university Bachelor's Programme Economics and Statistics

Sweden, Stockholm 01/2010 - 01/2013

Bachelor Thesis. "Two group classification and complex sampling design" A Graded.

- Double bachelors program.
- · Erasmus Scholarship. Exchange semester at a Business School in Lisbon, Nova School of Business and Economics.
- Internship: Styligh.com as Performance Marketing Manager, 6 months, Germany, Munich

Nova School of Business and Economics

Lisbon

Business School

2011 - 2012

- Exchange Studies with courses within the program Business Economics
- Erasmus Scholarship Grant

Languages

English Native ●●●●

Swedish Native ●●●●

German Intermediate ••••

Dutch Intermediate ••••

Skills

Google · All industries · Data · Al · Sales · Marketing · Growth · Business Development · Consumer Insight · CRM · E-commerce · Entrepreneurship · Management · Hubspot · Internet Of Things · IoT · Kpi · Lead Generation · Market Research · Oracle · Oracle · Cloud · SalesForce · Sas · Statistics

Courses & Certificates

Google AI Powered Ads Shopping Certification 2024

ORACLE Sales Academy 2016

ORACLE Sales Academy 2017

Interests & Hobbies

I actively engage in industry-related reading, focusing on business development, strategy, statistics, data, and economics.

I have a strong passion for health and wellness, with a background as a national-level athlete, which has honed my discipline, resilience, and dedication to performance.

I have a keen interest in market trends, particularly in technology, startups, and investments.

Volunteering

Stockholm Studentbostäder SSSB Boardmember

Jan 2012 - December 2012

Date period